Contact

4138224757 (Mobile) blake@integritymedicalstaff ingllc.com

www.linkedin.com/in/blakegaylord-944039164 (LinkedIn) integritymedicalstaffingIlc.com (Company) bit.ly/IntegrityApp (Other)

Top Skills

Basic Life Support (BLS) Medication Administration Vital Signs

Certifications
Licensed Practical Nurse

Blake Gaylord

Licensed Practical Nurse at Integrity Medical Staffing, LLC Cheshire, Massachusetts

Summary

I currently have been a Licensed Practical Nurse since March of 2015, with 3 years of it being a Travel Nurse and Co-Owner of a family-owned medical staffing agency. I've worked in 200 bed facilities as well as rural critical access hospitals in Alaska which included a facility in the Arctic Circle. I became an LPN at 19 years old and soon after opened up our family-owned business with my brother who is an RN and father who has a lengthy history in business management. Our business is different from any other agency because 2/3 owners are nurses and have worked at the facilities our staff will step foot in. Our desire to give Nurses and CNAs the pay they deserve while obtaining lifelong stories. Best of all, our company provides care to facilities in need of help. We are JCAHO accredited and continually push to further our knowledge and reach new goals.

Experience

Integrity Medical Staffing, LLC 3 years 11 months

Co-Owner

September 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months)

Licensed Practical Nurse

November 2019 - December 2019 (2 months)

Turners Falls, Massachusetts

I worked as an LPN Treatment and Med Nurse at a Psych Facility for a month helping during the Nursing shortage at the facility.

Licensed Practical Nurse November 2016 - March 2017 (5 months)

Kotzebue, Alaska

I worked at the LTC facility as we began our business at the first location.

Kotzebue is a large Native hub for surrounding villages. I learned a ton about the Inupiat culture/customs caring for roughly 15 residents with two CNAs at

night and 3 during the day. I did swing shifts often during my contract to help out where was needed.

RTG Medical Licensed Practical Nurse May 2016 - November 2016 (7 months) Turners Falls, MA

I worked as an LPN Treatment and Med Nurse at a Psych Facility for roughly 6 months while in school taking RN pre-regs.

INTEGRINURSE INC Licensed Practical Nurse April 2016 - November 2016 (8 months) Pittsfield, Massachusetts

Berkshire Health Systems Licensed Practical Nurse January 2015 - April 2016 (1 year 4 months) Pittsfield, Massachusetts Area

I worked over a year on the acute rehab/long term care unit as a staff nurse.

Education

Charles H McCann Technical School License, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (2014 - 2014)

Hoosac Valley Middle & High School High School Diploma · (2009 - 2013)